<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">CONVENE_YO</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>

    <string name="title_activity_test">test</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_registration">Registration</string>


    <!--chaitanya values-->

    <string name="Edit_text_1">Enter your full name</string>
    <string name="Text_view_1">Member 1</string>
    <string name="Text_view_2">Mobile no</string>
    <string name="Edit_text_2">+919876543210</string>
    <string name="Text_view_3">Email id</string>
    <string name="Edit_text_3">Active Email id</string>

    <string name="Text_view_5">Year</string>
    <string name="Year_prompt">Select your year</string>

    <string name="TE">TE</string>
    <string name="BE">BE</string>

    <string name="Text_view_4">Branch</string>
    <string name="Branch_prompt">Your Branch</string>

    <string name="Branch_1">Computer</string>
    <string name="Branch_2">IT</string>
    <string name="Branch_3">Electronics</string>
    <string name="Branch_4">Electrical</string>

    <string name="Text_view_6">College</string>
    <string name="College_prompt">Select your college</string>

    <string name="a4950">A P Shah Institute of Technology Thane</string>
    <string name="a5840">Abhinav Education Societys College of Engineering and Technology (Degree) Wadwadi</string>
    <string name="a8194">Adarsh Shikshan Prasarak Mandals K. T. Patil College of Engineering and Technology Osmanabad</string>
    <string name="a2547">Aditya Engineering College  Beed</string>
    <string name="a1376">Adsuls Technical Campus Chas Dist. Ahmednagar</string>
    <string name="a2553">Agnel Charities FR. C. Rodrigues Institute of Technology Vashi Navi Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a3730">Ahmednagar Jilha Maratha Vidya Prasarak Samajache Shri. Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj College of Engineering Nepti</string>
    <string name="a4907">Al-Ameen Educational and Medical Foundation College of Engineering Koregaon Bhima</string>
    <string name="a6083">Alard Charitable Trusts Alard College of Engineering and Management Pune</string>
    <string name="a7260">Aldel Education Trusts St. John College of Engineering and Management Vevoor Palghar</string>
    <string name="a1187">All India Shri Shivaji Memorial Societys College of Engineering Pune</string>
    <string name="a5776">All India Shri Shivaji Memorial Societys Institute of Information TechnologyPune</string>
    <string name="a2364">Amar Seva Mandals Shree Govindrao Vanjari College of Engineering and Technology Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a6953">Amruta Vaishnavi Education and Welfare Trusts Shatabdi Institute of Engineering and Research Agaskhind Tal. Sinnar</string>
    <string name="a3540">Amrutvahini Sheti and Shikshan Vikas Sansthas Amrutvahini College of Engineering Sangamner</string>
    <string name="a8129">Anantrao Pawar College of Engineering and Research Pune</string>
    <string name="a4717">Anjuman College of Engineering and Technology Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a1305">Anjuman-I-Islams Kalsekar Technical Campus Panvel</string>
    <string name="a5894">Anjuman-I-Islams M.H. Saboo Siddik College of Engineering Byculla Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a2482">Ankush Shikshan Sansthas G. H. Raisoni Institute of Engineering and Technology Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a7071">Ankush Shikshan Sansthas G.H.Raisoni College of Engineering Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a3659">Annasaheb Dange College of Engineering and Technology Ashta Sangli</string>
    <string name="a3007">Atharva College of EngineeringMalad(West)Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a1301">Aurangabad College of Engineering Naygaon Savangi Aurangabad</string>
    <string name="a7596">B.R. Harne College of Engineering and Technology Karav Tal-Ambernath.</string>
    <string name="a5890">B.R.A.C.Ts Vishwakarma Institute of Information Technology Kondhwa (Bk.) Pune</string>
    <string name="a4184">Balaghat Engineering CollegeRuddha Ahmedpur</string>
    <string name="a2478">Bansilal Ramnath Agarawal Charitable Trusts Vishwakarma Institute of Technology Bibwewadi Pune</string>
    <string name="a8773">Bhagwant Institute of Technology Barshi</string>
    <string name="a7067">Bharati Vidyapeeth College of Engineering Belpada Kharghar Navi Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a5361">Bharati Vidyapeeths College of Engineering for Women Katraj Dhankawadi Pune</string>
    <string name="a3655">Bharati Vidyapeeths College of Engineering Kolhapur</string>
    <string name="a1949">Bharati vidyapeeths Group of Institute. Lavale Technical Campus Mulshi Pune.</string>
    <string name="a8244">Bhartiya Vidya Bhavans Sardar Patel Institute of Technology  Andheri Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a6538">Bhausaheb Charitable Trusts Bhausaheb Mulik College of Engineering Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a4832">Bhonsla College of Engineering and Research Akola</string>
    <string name="a3126">Brahma Valley College of Engineering and Research Trimbakeshwar Nashik</string>
    <string name="a1420">Chhartrapati Shivaji Maharaj Institute of Technology Shedung Panvel</string>
    <string name="a7714">Choudhary Attar Singh Yadav Memorial TrustSiddhant College of Engineering Maval</string>
    <string name="a6008">College of Engineering and Technology North Maharashtra Knowledge City Jalgaon</string>
    <string name="a4302">College of Engineering Pune</string>
    <string name="a2596">College Of Engineering Vairag Tal. Barshi</string>
    <string name="a8891">CSMSS Chh. Shahu College of Engineering Aurangabad</string>
    <string name="a7185">Cummins College of Engineering For Women Sukhali (Gupchup) Tal. Hingna, Hingna Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a5479">D. Y. Patil College of Engineering Ambi Talegaon Maval</string>
    <string name="a2813">D. Y. Patil Institute of Engineering and Technology Ambi</string>
    <string name="a5960">D.Y. Patil College of Engineering and Technology Kolhapur</string>
    <string name="a1106">D.Y.Patil Education SocietysD.Y.Patil Technical Campus Faculty of Engineering and Faculty of ManagementTalsandeKolhapur.</string>
    <string name="a4254">Datta Meghe Institute of Medical Sciences Datta Meghe Institute of Engineering and Technology and Research Savangi (Meghe)</string>
    <string name="a7401">Dattajirao Kadam Technical Education Societys Textile and Engineering Institute Ichalkaranji.</string>
    <string name="a2548">Dattakala Group Of Institutions Swami - Chincholi Tal. Daund Dist. Pune</string>
    <string name="a5695">Deogiri Institute of Engineering and Management Studies Aurangabad</string>
    <string name="a8843">Department of Technology Shivaji University Kolhapur</string>
    <string name="a3989">Dhamangaon Education Societys College of Engineering and Technology Dhamangaon</string>
    <string name="a7137">Dhananjay Mahadik Group of Institutions Kagal Kolhapur</string>
    <string name="a2283">Dhole Patil Education Society Dhole Patil College of Engineering Wagholi Tal. Haveli</string>
    <string name="a5431">Dilkap Research Institute Of Engineering and Management Studies At.Mamdapur Post- Neral Tal- Karjat Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a8578">Dnyanshree Institute Engineering and Technology Satara</string>
    <string name="a3725">Don Bosco Institute of Technology Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a6872">Dr. A. D. Shinde College Of Engineering Tal.Gadhinglaj Kolhapur</string>
    <string name="a2019">Dr. Ashok Gujar Technical Institutes Dr. Daulatrao Aher College of Engineering Karad</string>
    <string name="a5166">Dr. Babasaheb Ambedkar College of Engineering and Research Wanadongri Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a8314">Dr. Babasaheb Ambedkar Technological University Lonere</string>
    <string name="a3460">Dr. Bhausaheb Nadurkar College of Engineering WaghapurYavatmal</string>
    <string name="a6608">Dr. D Y Patil Pratishthans College of Engineering Kolhapur</string>
    <string name="a1754">Dr. D. Y. Patil Educational Academys D.Y.Patil School of Engineering Academy Ambi</string>
    <string name="a4902">Dr. D. Y. Patil Pratishthans D.Y.Patil College of Engineering Akurdi Pune</string>
    <string name="a8049">Dr. D. Y. Patil School of Engineering and Technology Charholi(Bk) Via Lohgaon Pune</string>
    <string name="a3196">Dr. D. Y. Patil School OF Engineering Lohegaon Pune</string>
    <string name="a6343">Dr. D. Y. Patil Vidya Pratishthan Society Dr .D. Y. Patil Institute of Engineering and Technology PimpriPune</string>
    <string name="a1490">Dr. J. J. Magdum Charitable Trusts Dr. J.J. Magdum College of Engineering Jaysingpur</string>
    <string name="a4637">Dr.D.Y.Patil College Of Engineering and InnovationTalegaon</string>
    <string name="a7785">Dr.Rajendra Gode Institute of Technology and Research Amravati</string>
    <string name="a2931">Dwarka Bahu Uddeshiya Gramin Vikas Foundation Rajarshri Shahu College of Engineering Buldhana</string>
    <string name="a6079">Everest Education Society Group of Institutions (Integrated Campus) Ohar</string>
    <string name="a1225">Excelsior Education Societys K.C. College of Engineering and Management Studies and Research Kopri Thane (E)</string>
    <string name="a4373">Fabtech Technical Campus College of Engineering and Research Sangola</string>
    <string name="a7520">Flora Institute of Technology Khopi Near Khed Shivapur Toll Plaza Pune</string>
    <string name="a2667">Fr. Conceicao Rodrigues College of Engineering BandraMumbai</string>
    <string name="a5814">G. H. Raisoni College of Engineering and Management Ahmednagar</string>
    <string name="a8962">G. H.Raisoni Institute of Engineering and Technology Wagholi Pune</string>
    <string name="a4108">G. S. Mandals Maharashtra Institute of Technology Aurangabad</string>
    <string name="a7256">G.H. Raisoni college of Engineering and Management Amravati</string>
    <string name="a2402">G.H. Raisoni Institute of Engineering and Management Jalgaon</string>
    <string name="a5550">G.H.Raisoni Academy of Engineering and Technology Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a8697">G.H.Raisoni College of Engineering and Management Wagholi Pune</string>
    <string name="a3843">G.M.Vedak Institute of Technology Tala Raigad.</string>
    <string name="a6991">Geetai Charitable Trusts Khurana Sawant Institute of Engineering and Technology Balsond Hingoli.</string>
    <string name="a2137">Genba Sopanrao Moze College of Engineering Baner-Balewadi Pune</string>
    <string name="a5285">Genba Sopanrao Moze Trust Parvatibai Genba Moze College of EngineeringWagholi Pune</string>
    <string name="a8432">Genesis Insitute of Technology Kasarwadi Dist Kolhapur</string>
    <string name="a3579">Gharda Foundations Gharda Institute of TechnologyKhed Ratnagiri</string>
    <string name="a6726">Godavari Foundations Godavari College Of Engineering Jalgaon</string>
    <string name="a7778">Gokhale Education Societys R.H. Sapat College of Engineering Management Studies and Research Nashik</string>
    <string name="a5351">Gondia Education Societys Manoharbhai Patel Institute Of Engineering and Technology Shahapur Bhandara</string>
    <string name="a2924">Gondia Education Societys Manoharbhai Patel Institute of Engineering and Technology Gondia</string>
    <string name="a8498">Gourishankar Educational and Charitable Trusts Satara College of Engineering and Management Limb Satara</string>
    <string name="a6072">Government College of Engineering and Research Avasari Khurd</string>
    <string name="a3645">Government College of Engineering Amravati</string>
    <string name="a1218">Government College of Engineering Aurangabad</string>
    <string name="a6792">Government College of Engineering Chandrapur</string>
    <string name="a4366">Government College of Engineering Jalgaon</string>
    <string name="a1939">Government College of Engineering Karad</string>
    <string name="a7513">Government College of Engineering Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a5086">Gramodyogik Shikshan Mandals Marathwada Institute of Technology Aurangabad</string>
    <string name="a2660">Guru Gobind Singh College of Engineering and Research Centre Nashik.</string>
    <string name="a8234">Guru Nanak Institute of Engineering and TechnologyKalmeshwar Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a5807">Gurunanak Educational Societys Gurunanak Institute of Technology Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a3380">Haji Jamaluddin Thim Trusts Theem College of Engineering At. Villege Betegaon Boisar</string>
    <string name="a8954">Hindi Seva Mandals Shri Sant Gadgebaba College of Engineering and Technology Bhusawal</string>
    <string name="a6528">Hi-Tech Institute of Technology Aurangabad</string>
    <string name="a4101">Holy-Wood Academys Sanjeevan Engineering and Technology Institute Panhala</string>
    <string name="a1674">Hon. Shri. Babanrao Pachpute Vichardhara Trust Group of Institutions (Integrated Campus)-Parikrama Kashti Shrigondha</string>
    <string name="a7248">Hope Foundation and research centers Finolex Academy of Management and Technology Ratnagiri</string>
    <string name="a4822">I.S.B.and M. School of Technology Nande Village</string>
    <string name="a2395">Ideal Institute of Technology Wada Dist.Thane</string>
    <string name="a7969">Indira College of Engineering and Management Pune</string>
    <string name="a5542">Innovative Engineers and Teachers Education Societys Bharat College of Engineering Kanhor Badlapur(W)</string>
    <string name="a3116">Institute of Chemical Technology Matunga Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a8690">Institute Of Knowledge-College Of Engineering Pimpale - Jagtap</string>
    <string name="a6263">International Centre of Excellence in Engineering and Management Aurangabad.</string>
    <string name="a3836">International Institute of Information Technology (I2IT), Pune</string>
    <string name="a1410">ITM College of Engineering Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a6984">Jagadamba Education Soc. Nashiks S.N.D. College of Engineering and Reserch Babulgaon</string>
    <string name="a4557">Jagadambha Bahuuddeshiya Gramin Vikas Sansthas Jagdambha College of Engineering and Technology Yavatmal</string>
    <string name="a2130">Jai Mahakali Shikshan Sanstha Agnihotri College of Engineering Sindhi(Meghe)</string>
    <string name="a7705">Jaidev Education Society J D College of Engineering and Management Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a5278">Jaihind College Of EngineeringKuran</string>
    <string name="a2851">Jamia Institute Of Engineering And Management Studies Akkalkuwa</string>
    <string name="a8425">Janata Shikshan Prasarak Mandals Babasaheb Naik College Of Engineering, Pusad</string>
    <string name="a5999">Jawahar Education Societys Annasaheb Chudaman Patil College of EngineeringKharghar</string>
    <string name="a3572">Jawahar Education Societys Institute of Technology Management and Research Nashik.</string>
    <string name="a1145">Jawaharlal Darda Institute of Engineering and Technology Yavatmal</string>
    <string name="a6719">Jayawant Shikshan Prasarak Mandal Bhivarabai Sawant Institute of Technology and Research Wagholi</string>
    <string name="a4293">Jaywant College of Engineering and Management Kille Macchindragad Tal. Walva</string>
    <string name="a1866">Jaywant Shikshan Prasarak MandalsRajarshi Shahu College of Engineering Tathawade Pune</string>
    <string name="a7440">JMSS Shri Shankarprasad Agnihotri College of Engineering Wardha</string>
    <string name="a5013">JSPM Narhe Technical Campus Pune.</string>
    <string name="a2587">JSPMs Imperial College of Engineering and Research Wagholi Pune</string>
    <string name="a8161">JSPMs Jaywantrao Sawant College of Engineering Pune</string>
    <string name="a5734">K J Somaiya Institute of Engineering and Information Technology Sion Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a3307">K. C. E. Societys College of Engineering and Information Technology Jalgaon</string>
    <string name="a8882">K. E. Societys Rajarambapu Institute of Technology Walwa Sangli</string>
    <string name="a6455">K. J.s Educational Institut Trinity College of Engineering and Research Pisoli Haveli</string>
    <string name="a4028">K. K. Wagh Institute of Engineering Education and Research Nashik</string>
    <string name="a1601">K.D.K. College of Engineering Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a7175">K.D.M. Education Society Vidharbha Institute of TechnologyUmred Road Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a4749">K.J.s Educational Institutes K.J.College of Engineering and Management Research Pisoli</string>
    <string name="a2322">K.J.Somaiya College of Engineering Vidyavihar Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a7896">K.V.N. Naik S. P. Sansths Loknete Gopinathji Munde Institute of Engineering Education and Research Nashik.</string>
    <string name="a5469">Kai Amdar Bramhadevdada Mane Shikshan and Samajik Prathistans Bramhadevdada Mane Institute of Technology Solapur</string>
    <string name="a3043">Kalyani Charitable Trust Late Gambhirrao Natuba Sapkal College of Engineering Anjaneri Trimbakeshwar Road Nashik</string>
    <string name="a8617">Kavi Kulguru Institute of Technology and Science Ramtek</string>
    <string name="a6190">KDK College of Engineering Umrer Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a3763">Keystone School of Engineering Pune</string>
    <string name="a1337">KJEIs Trinity Academy of Engineering Yewalewadi Pune</string>
    <string name="a6911">Kolhapur Institute of Technology College of Engineering Kolhapur</string>
    <string name="a4484">Konkan Gyanpeeth College of Engineering Karjat</string>
    <string name="a2057">Koti Vidya Charitable Trusts Smt. Alamuri Ratnamala Institute of Engineering and Technology Sapgaon Tal. Shahapur</string>
    <string name="a7632">Krushi Jivan Vikas Pratishthan Ballarpur Institute of Technology Mouza Bamni</string>
    <string name="a5205">KSGBSs Bharat- Ratna Indira Gandhi College of Engineering Kegaon Solapur</string>
    <string name="a2778">Late Shri. Vishnu Waman Thakur Charitable Trust Viva Institute of Technology Shirgaon</string>
    <string name="a8352">Laxminarayan Institute of Technology Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a5926">Leela Education Society G.V. Acharya Institute of Engineering and Technology Shelu Karjat</string>
    <string name="a3499">Let.Dr.D.B.Dod College of Engineering JamblaAchalpur</string>
    <string name="a1072">Lokmanya Tilak College of Engineering Kopar Khairane Navi Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a6646">Lokmanya Tilak Jankalyan Shiksan Sanstha Priyadarshini Indira Gandhi College of Engineering Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a4220">Lokmanya Tilak Jankalyan Shikshan Sanstha Priyadarshani College of Engineering Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a1793">Lokmanya Tilak Jankalyan Shikshan Sansthas  Priyadarshini Institute of Engineering and Technology Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a7367">Lokmanya Tilak Jankalyan Shikshan Sastha Priyadarshini J. L. College Of Engineering Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a4940">Loknete Hanumantrao Charitable Trusts Adarsh Institute of Technology and Research Centre VitaSangli</string>
    <string name="a2514">M.D. Yergude Memorial Shikshan Prasarak Mandals Shri Sai College of Engineering and Technology Badravati</string>
    <string name="a8088">M.G.M.s College of Engineering and Technology Kamothe Navi Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a5661">M.G.M.s Jawaharlal Nehru Engineering College Aurangabad</string>
    <string name="a3234">M.S. Bidve Engineering College Latur</string>
    <string name="a8809">MAEERs M.I.T. College of Engineering  Kothrud Pune</string>
    <string name="a6382">Maharashtra College of Engineering Betada Brahmapuri</string>
    <string name="a3955">Maharashtra College of Engineering Nilanga</string>
    <string name="a1528">Maharashtra Education Societys Maharashtra Udayagiri Institute of Management and Technology Somnathpur</string>
    <string name="a7103">Maharashtra Institute of Technology Kothrud Pune</string>
    <string name="a4676">Mahatma Basaweshwar Education Societys College of Engineering Ambejogai</string>
    <string name="a2249">Mahatma Education Societys Pillai College of Engineering New Panvel</string>
    <string name="a7823">Mahatma Education Societys Pillai HOC College of Engineering and Technology Tal. Khalapur. Dist. Raigad</string>
    <string name="a5397">Mahatma Gandhi Missions College of Engineering Hingoli Rd Nanded.</string>
    <string name="a2970">Mahavir Education Trusts Shah and Anchor Kutchhi Engineering College Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a8544">Maitraya Education Society Nagarjuna Institute of Engineering Technology and Management Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a6117">Manajiraje Bhosale Technical Campus Urun Islampur</string>
    <string name="a2728">Manav School of Engineering and Technology Gut No. 1035 Nagpur Surat Highway NH No. 6 Tal.Vyala Balapur Akola 444302</string>
    <string name="a5558">Mandar Education Societys Rajaram Shinde College of Engineering Pedhambe</string>
    <string name="a8303">Manjara Charitable Trusts Rajiv Gandhi Institute of Technology Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a3046">Marathwada Mitra Mandals College of Engineering Karvenagar Pune</string>
    <string name="a5876">Marathwada Mitra Mandals Institute of Technology Lohgaon Pune</string>
    <string name="a8706">Marathwada Shikshan Prasarak Mandals Shri Shivaji Institute of Engineering and Management Studies Parbhani</string>
    <string name="a3449">Matoshri College of Engineering and Research Centre Eklahare Nashik</string>
    <string name="a6193">Matoshri Pratishans Group of Institutions (Integrated Campus) Kupsarwadi  Nanded</string>
    <string name="a1022">Matsyodari Shikshan Sansathas College of Engineering and Technology Jalna</string>
    <string name="a3852">Maulana Mukhtar Ahmad Nadvi Technical Campus Malegaon.</string>
    <string name="a6597">Mauli Group of Institutions College of Engineering and Technology Shegaon.</string>
    <string name="a1340">MET Bhujbal Knowledge City MET Leagues Engineering College Adgaon Nashik.</string>
    <string name="a4170">Metropolitan Institute of Technology and Management Sukhalwad Sindhudurg.</string>
    <string name="a7000">MIT Academy of EngineeringAlandi Pune</string>
    <string name="a1743">MKSSSs Cummins College of Engineering for Women KarvenagarPune</string>
    <string name="a4487">Modern Education Societys College of Engineering Pune</string>
    <string name="a7317">N. B. Navale Sinhgad College of Engineering Kegaon solapur</string>
    <string name="a2146">N.Y.S.S.s Datta Meghe College of Engineering Airoli Navi Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a4891">Nagaon Education Societys Gangamai College of Engineering Nagaon Tal Dist Dhule</string>
    <string name="a7635">Nagnathappa Halge Engineering College Parli Beed</string>
    <string name="a2464">Nanasaheb Mahadik College of EngineeringWalwa Sangli.</string>
    <string name="a5294">Nashik District Maratha Vidya Prasarak Samajs Karmaveer Adv.Babaurao Ganpatrao Thakare College of Engineering Nashik</string>
    <string name="a8038">National Institute of Electronics and Information Technology(NIELIT) Aurangabad.</string>
    <string name="a2781">National Power Training Institute Nagpur (Under the Ministry of Power(Govt. of India)</string>
    <string name="a5611">Nav Disha Education Soc Acharya Vinoba Bhave Institute of Technology Mauza-PawnarWardha</string>
    <string name="a8441">Navsahyadri Education Societys Group of Institutions</string>
    <string name="a3185">NBN Sinhgad Technical Institutes Campus Pune</string>
    <string name="a5929">New Horizon Institute of Technology and Management(Womens College) Thane</string>
    <string name="a8759">Nutan Maharashtra Vidya Prasarak Mandal Nutan Maharashtra Institute of Engineering andTechnology Talegaon station Pune</string>
    <string name="a3588">Om Arunodaya Bahuuddeshiya Khadi Garmudyog Vikas Sansthas Om College of Engineering Inzapur Wardha</string>
    <string name="a6332">P. R. Pote (Patil) Education and Welfare Trusts Group of Institution(Integrated Campus) Amravati</string>
    <string name="a1075">P.K. Technical Campus Pune.</string>
    <string name="a3905">P.R. Patil College of Engineering and Technology Amravati</string>
    <string name="a6735">P.S.G.V.P. Mandals D.N. Patel College of Engineering Shahada Dist. Nandurbar</string>
    <string name="a1479">Pad. Dr.D.Y.Patil Institute of Engineering Management and Reseach Akurdi Pune</string>
    <string name="a4223">Padmabhushan Vasantdada Patil Pratishthans College of Engineering SionMumbai</string>
    <string name="a7053">Padmashri Dr. V.B. Kolte College of Engineering Malkapur Buldhana</string>
    <string name="a1882">Padmashri Dr. Vithalrao Vikhe Patil College of Engineering Ahmednagar</string>
    <string name="a4626">Paramhansa Ramkrishna Maunibaba Shikshan Santhas  Anuradha Engineering College Chikhali</string>
    <string name="a7370">Peoples Education Societys College of Engineering Aurangabad</string>
    <string name="a2199">Phaltan Education Societys College of Engineering Thakurki Tal- Phaltan Dist-Satara</string>
    <string name="a5029">Pimpri Chinchwad Education Trust Pimpri Chinchwad College of Engineering Pune</string>
    <string name="a7773">Pimpri Chinchwad Education Trusts Pimpri Chinchwad College Of Engineering And Research Ravet</string>
    <string name="a2517">Pradnya Niketan Education Societys Nagesh Karajagi Orchid College of Engineering and Technology Solapur</string>
    <string name="a5347">Pratap Institute of Management and Technology Washim.</string>
    <string name="a8177">Pravara Rural College of Engineering Loni Pravaranagar Ahmednagar.</string>
    <string name="a2920">Pravara Rural Education Societys Sir Visvesvaraya Institute of Technology Chincholi Dist. Nashik</string>
    <string name="a5664">Priyadarshini Bhagwati College of Engineering Harpur Nagar Umred RoadNagpur</string>
    <string name="a8494">Prof Ram Meghe College of Engineering and Management Badnera</string>
    <string name="a3323">Prof. Ram Meghe Institute of Technology and Research Amravati</string>
    <string name="a6067">Progressive Education Societys Modern College of Engineering Pune</string>
    <string name="a8812">Pune District Education Associations College of Engineering Pune</string>
    <string name="a3641">Pune Institute of Computer Technology Dhankavdi Pune</string>
    <string name="a6471">Pune Vidyarthi Grihas College of Engineering and Technology Pune</string>
    <string name="a1214">Pune Vidyarthi Grihas College Of Engineering Nashik</string>
    <string name="a3958">R. C. Patel Institute of Technology Shirpur</string>
    <string name="a6788">R.V. Parankar College of Engineering and Technology Arvi Dist Wardha</string>
    <string name="a1617">Rajendra Mane College of Engineering and Technology Ambav Deorukh</string>
    <string name="a4361">Rajgad Dnyanpeeths Technical CampusDhangwadi Bhor</string>
    <string name="a7106">Rajiv Gandhi College of Engineering and Research Hingna Road Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a1935">Rajiv Gandhi College of Engineering At Post Karjule Hariya Tal.Parner Dist.Ahmednagar</string>
    <string name="a4765">Rajiv Gandhi College of Engineering Research and Technology Chandrapur</string>
    <string name="a7509">Ramrao Adik Edu Soc Ramarao Adik Institute of Tech. Navi Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a2252">Rasiklal M. Dhariwal Sinhgad Technical Institutes Campus Warje Pune.</string>
    <string name="a5082">Rayat Shikshan Sansthas Karmaveer Bhaurao Patil College of Engineering Satara</string>
    <string name="a7912">Rizvi Education Societys Rizvi College of Engineering BandraMumbai</string>
    <string name="a2655">S K N Sinhgad College of Engineering Korti Tal. Pandharpur Dist Solapur</string>
    <string name="a5400">S.D.N.C.R.E.Ss.Late Narayandas Bhawandas Chhabada Institute of Engineering and Technology Satara</string>
    <string name="a8230">S.I.E.S. Graduate School of Technology Nerul Navi Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a3058">S.S.P.M.s College of Engineering Kankavli</string>
    <string name="a5803">Sahakar Maharshee Shankarrao Mohite Patil Institute of Technology and Research Akluj</string>
    <string name="a8547">Sahyadri Valley College of Engineering and Technology Rajuri Pune.</string>
    <string name="a3376">Sai Institute of Engineering and Technology Bilda Aurangabad.</string>
    <string name="a6206">Samarth Education Trusts Arvind Gavali College Of Engineering Panwalewadi VaryeSatara.</string>
    <string name="a8950">Samarth Group of Institutions Bangarwadi Post Belhe Tal. Junnar Dist. Pune</string>
    <string name="a3694">Samridhi Sarwajanik Charitable Trust Jhulelal Institute of Technology Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a6524">Sandip Foundation Sandip Institute of Technology and Research Centre Mahiravani Nashik</string>
    <string name="a1352">Sandip Foundations Sandip Institute of Engineering and Management Nashik</string>
    <string name="a4097">Sanghavi College of Engineering Varvandi Nashik.</string>
    <string name="a6841">Sanjay Education Societys College of Engineering Navalnagar</string>
    <string name="a1670">Sanjivani Rural Education Societys Sanjivani College of Engineering Kopargaon</string>
    <string name="a4500">Sanmarg Shikshan Sanstha Mandukarrao Pandav College of Engineering BhandaraNagpur</string>
    <string name="a7244">Sanmarg Shikshan Sansthas Smt. Radhikatai Pandav College of Engineering Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a1988">Sanmati Engineering College Sawargaon Barde Washim</string>
    <string name="a4818">Sant Gadge Baba Amravati UniversityAmravati</string>
    <string name="a7647">Sant Gajanan Maharaj College of Engineering Gadhinglaj</string>
    <string name="a2391">Saraswati Education Society Group of Institutions ( Integrated Campus) Diksal Dist. Raigad</string>
    <string name="a5135">Saraswati Education Society Yadavrao Tasgaonkar College of Engineering and Management Nasarapur Chandai Karjat</string>
    <string name="a7965">Saraswati Education Society Yadavrao Tasgaonkar Institute of Engineering and Technology Karjat</string>
    <string name="a2794">Saraswati Education Societys Saraswati College of EngineeringKharghar Navi Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a5538">Sardar Patel College of Engineering Andheri</string>
    <string name="a8283">Sardar Patel Memorial Societys Namdevrao Poreddiwar College of Engineering and Technology Gadchiroli</string>
    <string name="a3112">Sarvasiddhanta Education Socs Nuva College of Engineering and Technology Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a5941">Shahajirao Patil Vikas Pratishthan S.B.Patil College of Engineering Vangali Tal. Indapur</string>
    <string name="a8686">Shanti Education Society A.G. Patil Institute of Technology Soregaon Solapur(North)</string>
    <string name="a3429">Sharad Institute of Technology College of Engineering Yadrav(Ichalkaranji)</string>
    <string name="a6259">Shetkari Shikshan Mandals Pad. Vasantraodada Patil Institute of Technology Budhgaon Sangli</string>
    <string name="a1088">Shivajirao S. Jondhale College of Engineering DombivaliMumbai</string>
    <string name="a3832">Shivganga Charitable Trust Sangli Vishveshwarya Technical Campus Faculty of Degree Engineering Patgaon Miraj</string>
    <string name="a6577">Shivnagar Vidya Prasarak Mandals College of Engineering Malegaon-Baramati</string>
    <string name="a1406">Shramsadhana Bombay Trust College of Engineering and Technology Jalgaon</string>
    <string name="a4235">Shree Bapuraoji Deshmukh Foundation Suresh Deshmukh College of Engineering Selukate Wardha</string>
    <string name="a6980">Shree Gajanan Maharaj Shikshan Prasarak Mandals Sharadchandra Pawar College of Engineering Dumbarwadi</string>
    <string name="a1723">Shree L.R. Tiwari College of Engineering Mira Road Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a4553">Shree Ramchandra College of Engineering LonikandPune</string>
    <string name="a7383">Shree Saibaba Institute of Engineering Research and Allied Sciences Rahta.</string>
    <string name="a2126">Shree Tuljabhavani College of Engineering Tuljapur</string>
    <string name="a4871">Shree Yash Pratishthan Shreeyash College of Engineering and Technology Aurangabad</string>
    <string name="a7701">Shri Chhatrapati Shivaji College of Engineering (Rahuri Factory) Tal.Rahuri Dist.Ahmednagar</string>
    <string name="a2529">Shri Gulabrao Deokar College of Engineering Jalgaon</string>
    <string name="a5274">Shri Guru Gobind Singhji Institute of Engineering and Technology Nanded</string>
    <string name="a8018">Shri Hanuman Vyayam Prasarak Mandals College of Engineering and Technology Amravati</string>
    <string name="a2847">Shri Pandurang Pratishtan Karmayogi Engineering College Shelve Pandharpur</string>
    <string name="a5677">Shri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering and Management Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a8421">Shri Sai Samajik Vikas Santhas Shri Sai Colllege of Engineering Paddari Village Tal. and Dist. Aurangabad</string>
    <string name="a3165">Shri Sant Gajanan Maharaj College of EngineeringShegaon</string>
    <string name="a5994">Shri Shivaji Education Societys College of Engineering and Technology Akola</string>
    <string name="a8824">Shri Shivaji Vidya Prasarak Sansthas Late Bapusaheb Shivaji Rao Deore College of EngineeringDhule</string>
    <string name="a3568">Shri Vile Parle Kelvani Mandals Dwarkadas J. Sanghvi College of Engineering Vile ParleMumbai</string>
    <string name="a6312">Shri Vithal Education and Research Institutes College of Engineering Pandharpur</string>
    <string name="a1141">Shri. Ambabai Talim Sansthas Sanjay Bhokare Group of Institutes Miraj</string>
    <string name="a3971">Shri. Balasaheb Mane Prasarak Mandals Ashokrao Mane Group of Institutions Kolhapur</string>
    <string name="a6715">Shri. Dadasaheb Gawai Charitable Trusts Dr. Smt. Kamaltai Gawai Institute of Engineering and Technology Darapur Amravati</string>
    <string name="a1459">Shri. Jaykumar Rawal Institute of Technology Dondaicha.</string>
    <string name="a4288">Shri. Sai Shikshan Sanstha Nagpur Institute of Technology Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a7118">Shri.Someshwar Shikshan Prasarak Mandals Someshwar Engineering College Someshwar Nagar</string>
    <string name="a1862">Shrimati Rajashri Mulak College of Engineering for Womens Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a4606">Shriram Gram Vikas Shikshan Sanstha Vilasrao Deshmukh College of Engineering and Technology Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a7436">Shriram Institute Of Engineering And Technology Centre Paniv</string>
    <string name="a2265">Siddhivinayak Technical Campus School of Engineering and Research Technology Shirasgon Nile</string>
    <string name="a5009">Sinhagad Institute of Technology Lonavala</string>
    <string name="a7754">Sinhgad Academy of Engineering Kondhwa (BK) Kondhwa-Saswad Road Pune</string>
    <string name="a2582">Sinhgad College of Engineering Vadgaon (BK) Pune</string>
    <string name="a5412">Sinhgad Technical Education Society Sinhgad Institute of Technology and Science Narhe (Ambegaon)</string>
    <string name="a8157">Sinhgad Technical Education Societys Smt. Kashibai Navale College of EngineeringVadgaonPune</string>
    <string name="a2900">Sipna Shikshan Prasarak Mandal College of Engineering and Technology Amravati</string>
    <string name="a5730">Sir Shantilal Badjate Charitable Trusts S. B. Jain Institute of technology Management and Research Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a8560">SKN Sinhgad Institute of Technology and Science Kusgaon(BK)Pune.</string>
    <string name="a3303">Smt. Indira Gandhi College of EngineeringKopar Khairane Navi Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a6048">SNJBs Late Sau. Kantabai Bhavarlalji Jain College of Engineering (Jain Gurukul) NeminagarChandwad(Nashik)</string>
    <string name="a8877">Sou. Sushila Danchand Ghodawat Cha.Trusts Sanjay Ghodavat Group of Institution (Integrated Campus) Atigre Kolhapur</string>
    <string name="a3706">St. Francis Institute of TechnologyBorivali Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a6451">ST. Vincent Pallotti College of Engineering and Technology Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a1194">STMEIs Sandipani Technical Campus-Faculty of Engineering Latur.</string>
    <string name="a4024">Suman Ramesh Tulsiani Technical Campus: Faculty of Engineering KamshetPune.</string>
    <string name="a6854">Suryodaya College of Engineering and Technology Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a1597">T.M.E. Societys J.T.Mahajan College of Engineering Faizpur</string>
    <string name="a4342">Tatyasaheb Kore Institute of Engineering and Technology Warananagar</string>
    <string name="a7171">Terna Engineering College Nerul Navi Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a2000">Terna Public Charitable Trusts College of Engineering Osmanabad</string>
    <string name="a4745">Thadomal Shahani Engineering College Bandra Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a7489">Thakur College of Engineering and Technology Kandivali Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a2318">The Shetkari Shikshan Mandal Sanglis Pd. Vasantdada Patil Institute of Technology Bavdhan Pune</string>
    <string name="a5148">TSSMs Bhivarabai Sawant College of Engineering and Research Narhe Pune</string>
    <string name="a7892">Universal College of Engineering and Research Sasewadi</string>
    <string name="a2636">Universal College of EngineeringKaman Dist. Thane</string>
    <string name="a5465">University Department of Chemical Technology Aurangabad</string>
    <string name="a8295">University Institute of Chemical Technology North Maharashtra University Jalgaon</string>
    <string name="a3039">Usha Mittal Institute of Technology SNDT Womens University Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a5783">V M Institute of Engineering and Technology Dongargaon Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a8613">V.J. Shinde College of Engineering Osmanabad.</string>
    <string name="a3442">Veermata Jijabai Technological Institute(VJTI) Matunga Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a6186">Vidarbha Bahu-Uddeshiya Shikshan Sansthas Tulshiramji Gaikwad Patil College of Engineering and Technology Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a8930">Vidharbha Bahu uddeshiya Shikshan Sansthas Abha Gaikwad ? Patil College of Engineering, Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a3759">Vidya Niketan College of Engineering Bota Sangamner</string>
    <string name="a6589">Vidya Niketan Institute of Engineering and Technology Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a1333">Vidya Prasarini Sabhas College of Engineering and Technology Lonavala</string>
    <string name="a4077">Vidya Pratishthans Kamalnayan Bajaj Institute of Engineering and Technology Baramati Dist.Pune</string>
    <string name="a6907">Vidya Vikas Pratishthan Institute of Engineering and Technology Solapur</string>
    <string name="a1736">Vidyalankar Institute of TechnologyWadala Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a4480">Vidyavardhinis College of Engineering and Technology Vasai Thane</string>
    <string name="a7224">Vighnaharata Trusts Shivajirao S. Jondhale College of Engineering and Technology Shahapur Asangaon Dist Thane</string>
    <string name="a2053">Vilasrao Deshmukh Foundation Group of Institutions Latur</string>
    <string name="a4883">Vishvatmak Jangli Maharaj Ashram Trusts Vishvatmak Om Gurudev College of Engineering Mohili-Aghai Shahpur.</string>
    <string name="a7628">Vishwabharati Academys College of Engineering Ahmednagar</string>
    <string name="a2371">Vishwaniketans Institute of Management Entrepreneurship and Engineering Technology(i MEET) Khalapur Dist Raigad</string>
    <string name="a5201">Vision Buldhana Educational and Welfare Societys Pankaj Laddhad Institute of Technology and Management Studies Yelgaon</string>
    <string name="a8031">Vivekanand Education Societys Institute of Technology Chembur Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a2774">VPMs Maharshi Parshuram College of Engineering Velneshwar Ratnagiri.</string>
    <string name="a5518">Wainganga College of Engineering and Management Dongargaon Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a8348">Walchand College of Engineering Sangli</string>
    <string name="a3177">Walchand Institute of Technology Solapur</string>
    <string name="a5922">Watumull Institute of Electronics Engineering and Computer Technology Worli Mumbai</string>
    <string name="a8666">Xavier Institute Of Engineering C/O Xavier Technical InstituteMahimMumbai</string>
    <string name="a3495">Yashoda Technical Campus Wadhe Satara.</string>
    <string name="a6325">Yashwant Rural Education Societys Bapurao Deshmukh Engineering CollegeSevagram</string>
    <string name="a1068">Yeshwantrao Chavan College of EngineeringWanadongri Nagpur</string>
    <string name="a3812">Zeal Education Societys Zeal College of Engineering and Reserch Narhe Pune</string>

    <string name="Text_view_7">City</string>

    <string name="Edit_text_4">City in which your college is located</string>

    <string name="header1">Team Members</string>
    <string name="header2">Project Details</string>

    <string name="Text_view_8">Project Title</string>
    <string name="Edit_text_5">Enter your full Project Title</string>

    <string name="Text_view_9">Project Domain</string>
    <string name="Domain_prompt">Choose Project Domain</string>

    <string name="Domain1">Data Mining</string>
    <string name="Domain2">IOT</string>
    <string name="Domain3">Image Processing</string>
    <string name="Domain4">Web Application</string>
    <string name="Domain5">Networking / Security</string>
    <string name="Domain6">Cloud Computing</string>
    <string name="Domain7">VLSI</string>
    <string name="Domain8">Embeded</string>
    <string name="Domain9">Robotics</string>
    <string name="Domain10">Artificial Intelligence / Machine Learning</string>

    <string name="Text_view_10">Guide Name</string>
    <string name="Edit_text_6">Enter your guide name</string>

</resources>
